meebome.com 2013-06-10

# Privacy Policy | meebo

**MEEBO.COM**   
**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last updated: December 3, 2012

**What this Privacy Policy covers**

This Privacy Policy applies to all services offered by Meebo, including the Meebo Bar. By visiting Meebo's website or using Meebo's services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites, products or services that are not owned or operated by Meebo or to actions taken by Meebo users. For example, this Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites where the Meebo Bar appears or to any third-party applications, social networks or social plug-in providers that you interact with via the Meebo services, all of which are governed by their own privacy policies.

**Information that Meebo collects**

When you interact with Meebo, we may ask for your name and email address. If you use the hosted instant messaging (IM) service provided within certain Meebo services ("Hosted Chat Feature"), the website service on which the Hosted Chat Feature is used may send us information about you, including your name, username at those services, unique user ID for those services, friends list, status, profile information, age and gender.

Meebo, like most other websites, automatically collects information about you and your activity (known as "log data"), including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser or device type, your interactions with Meebo, your interactions with third party social networks through Meebo, your geographic region and Meebo cookies associated with your browser. If you visit a site that has the Meebo Bar, we also collect information about the website or web page that you view and your interactions with that site. Meebo stores and uses this log data based on an anonymous identifier.

Meebo also uses cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with Meebo services. For instance, cookies are used to provide you with a better Meebo experience, to help us with our analytics, and to deliver and report on advertising that runs on Meebo services. Third-party advertising companies may also use cookies to collect data about you for the purpose of showing customized advertising to you when you use our services; you can opt out of such customized advertising here. You can also disable cookies or otherwise manage them through tools provided with your browser software and with third-party software packages.

Meebo uses the information it collects to provide, analyze and improve the Meebo services and to contact you as described under "Emails and other notifications."

**Sharing of information**

Meebo may share your non-public personally identifiable information with third parties in the following cases:

  * When we have your consent;
  * Where we have a good faith belief that it is required in order to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to prevent fraud or imminent harm, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * In order to provide certain functionality (such as abuse reporting or blocking of users) of the Hosted Chat Feature, we may share personal information, including your user ID used in connection with the Hosted Chat Feature, with the host website on which the Hosted Chat Feature is offered;
  * In the event that Meebo is acquired by or merged with another company or transfers substantially all of its assets to another company, Meebo may transfer all of its user information and data, including information about you, to that other company.

Meebo may share your public information or any anonymous information publicly or with Meebo's partners.

**Emails and other notifications**

Meebo reserves the right to send you communications relating to your account and the Meebo services. You can elect not to receive certain marketing messages from Meebo by email, but you cannot elect not to receive administrative messages relating to your account or legal matters. You consent to receiving all legally-required notifications from Meebo through display on Meebo's website or the Meebo services or through the email associated with your Meebo account.

**Non-U.S. users; EU Safe Harbor**

Meebo is hosted and operated entirely in the United States and is subject to United States law. Any personal information that you provide to Meebo is being provided to Meebo solely in the United States and will be hosted on United States servers. You consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States. If you are accessing Meebo from outside the United States, please be advised that United States law may not offer the same privacy protections as the law of your jurisdiction.

Meebo complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Meebo has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Meebo's certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

Meebo has committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If a complaint or dispute under the Safe Harbor Principles cannot be resolved through our internal process, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted at this URL (www.meebo.com/privacy/full/) or any successor URL.

**Editing and deleting your account information**

Deleting your Meebo account does not currently automatically remove your personally identifiable information from the Meebo servers. However, if you delete your account, we will use your personally identifiable information only to comply with legal requests as described under "Sharing of information." If you would like to have your personally identifiable information edited or deleted, please contact us as provided under "Comments and Questions."

**Comments and Questions**

Anyone who has any questions or concerns about this privacy policy can contact Meebo Customer Service at [dashboard-support@meebo-inc.com](mailto:dashboard-support@meebo-inc.com).
